<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ens on MDL - Talent Hub Blog</title>
    <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ens on MDL - Talent Hub Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://mdl.wtf/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>MDL Ghana Photoshoot 2021</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2021-04-15-mdl-ghana-photoshot-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2021-04-15-mdl-ghana-photoshot-2021/</guid>
      <description>MDL Ghana had its first photo shoot at Ada in the greater Accra region of Ghana as part of its talent expedition and preparation to launch in Africa for the first time.
Your browser does not support the video tag.  I must say it was indeed a very memorable moment. An event that will take decades to forget.
   MDL Talent Hub MDL Ghana Ada 2021                        MDL Talent Hub MDL Ghana Ada 2021                     Along with the photo shoot there was a brief interview of each of the talents and models as a whole, also, the photo shoots includes beach wear, African print casual and western world outfits.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MDL Desktop Wallet v0.27.1 Release</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2021-03-31-mdl-desktop-wallet-v0.27.1-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2021-03-31-mdl-desktop-wallet-v0.27.1-release/</guid>
      <description>We are happy to announce some important updates this week, including new versions of our desktop wallet and key improvements on the UX/UI front. This version of wallet supports Skycoin&amp;rsquo;s hardware wallet. Also includes all the features of Skycoin&amp;rsquo;s version 0.27.
The wallet has been updated from 0.26.1 -&amp;gt; 0.27.1, including changes and improvements in step with Skycoin wallet developments. Among the multiple updates are:
Added  Updated electron from version 2 to version 10, with many security fixes Add createRawTransactionV2 CLI command, which calls the API of /wallet/transaction to create the transaction and can create then unsigned transaction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MDL Talent Hub 2020 Revival</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2020-07-15-mdl-2020-revival/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2020-07-15-mdl-2020-revival/</guid>
      <description>Hello all new friends and our dear community members, here are the latest updates of our project. We all know it has been a difficult time for everyone, but we have still been working very hard to keep, maintain and develop everything we have achieved so far. It is time for announcing and showing some of our latest work. Please keep up.
MDL Talent Hub has always been and continue going mobile:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MDL in Ghana @ Chale Wote Festival 2019</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2019-09-14-mdl-in-ghana-chale-wote-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2019-09-14-mdl-in-ghana-chale-wote-2019/</guid>
      <description>The Annual CHALE WOTE Street Art Festival is the collective effort of many young people, from artists, musicians, filmmakers, writers and designers to students and activists&amp;hellip; It draws an average of over two thousand art lovers to the streets of James Town each year, and this year promises to be no different.
 The purpose of the festival is to promote the exhibition of alternative art in Ghana and to nurture an appreciation for different kinds of art among Ghanaians.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MDL Development update - August</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2019-08-22-mdl-development-update-aug/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2019-08-22-mdl-development-update-aug/</guid>
      <description>MDL IOs Wallet is being developed We are super proud to announce that the new MDL IOs Wallet is being developed and its already functional. We are now in process of opening a new developer account on Apple store and getting all the approvals, so hang in there, this may take a little while! :)
We are going to walk you around, please feel free to grab a seat and enjoy the show!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MDL Development update - July</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2019-07-24-mdl-development-update-july/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2019-07-24-mdl-development-update-july/</guid>
      <description>MDL Android Wallet version 0.3.5 Released New version (0.3.5) of MDL Android Wallet just hit Google Play and available for everybody.
Several security improvements and bug fixes incorporated.
&amp;ndash;
Download MDL now and be part of our growing community, HERE IS HOW:
&amp;ndash;
1) Install the wallet from Google Play:
https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=live.mdl.wallet
 2) Send tokens:
 On this new release, the sending view shows USD price in Send screen as well as in each wallet details page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Help MDL Make It to Ghana for Chale Wote 2019</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2019-06-12-mdl-chale-wote-2019-crowdfund/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2019-06-12-mdl-chale-wote-2019-crowdfund/</guid>
      <description>One of our active supporters in Ghana wants to show MDL Talent Hub again at this festival in August 2019, our team is super excited with the idea of having the budget to support this awesome activity with the help of our community! We’d like to help crowd fund him!
Here’s what he told us:
The CHALE WOTE Street Art Festival is an alternative platform that brings art, poets, models, actors, filmmakers, musicians, designers, dancers, and performers out onto the streets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MDL Talent Hub - Development update 2019 (part III)</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2019-05-03-mdl-dev-update-part-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2019-05-03-mdl-dev-update-part-3/</guid>
      <description>This month we are happy to announce progress on UX design and business analysis and the completion of end-to-end flows for bookers, parents, agencies and talents.
While digital is changing the world of work, how you successfully grow your career in the digital age has become the hottest topic in international business. Our online business will help, further your career with communication and networking. Whether you’re a talent preparing to expand your network, or you’re looking for talents for supporting your projects, in this article, we will guide your way to achieve the goals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MDL Talent Hub - Development update 2019 (part II)</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2019-04-02-mdl-dev-update-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2019-04-02-mdl-dev-update-part-2/</guid>
      <description>In part one of our extended update for 2019 a few weeks ago we announced that we were starting migration to Desktop Wallet v0.25, along with other developments for the first part of the year. This time we are happy to bring news that migration is complete and v0.25 has launched, with new fixes and features that make trading MDL a better way to pay and be paid for any talent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MDL New Year 2019 Chess Championship | The Winner Is</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2019-03-11-mdl-chess-champ-winner-is/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2019-03-11-mdl-chess-champ-winner-is/</guid>
      <description>It’s tough to get people from around the world together for one competition, but that’s what we did for the MDL New Year Chess tournament. The final games have now been played and our winners are in! Check out the final rankings and prizes below!
 The history of the games played during the championship is available HERE
Many thanks to all who made time in their schedules to connect with each other across time zones, and congratulations to our winners!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MDL Token XBTS.io DEX Increased price 2321.31% in 24h.</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2019-03-07-mdl-first-days-trading-xbts-mooning/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2019-03-07-mdl-first-days-trading-xbts-mooning/</guid>
      <description>Are you a new MDL trader? Lets together take our first steps towards learning the basics of trading should have access to multiple sources of quality education. Just like riding a bike, trial and error coupled with the ability to keep pressing forth will eventually lead to success.
One great advantage of MDL is that we only trade on Decentralized Exchanges. What are the advantages of trading MDL in a Decentralized Exchange compared to other regular exchanges ?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>March 8th, 2019 | MDL Talent Hub Hamburg Meet-up @ WeWork Labs</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2019-03-06-mdl-hamburg-ww-labs-meetup-invitation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2019-03-06-mdl-hamburg-ww-labs-meetup-invitation/</guid>
      <description>Please feel invited and join us this Friday, if you happen to be in Hamburg, Germany.
Meetup.com Event:
https://www.meetup.com/Friends-of-WeWork-Labs-Hamburg/events/259502829
(German below)
Apply your talent in a new way!
MDL Talent Hub is a completely new way to skilfully promote your talent and organise it for gigs via a secure Blockchain based system. Data is protected against third parties by the platform. The payment runs through the MDL tokens which guarantee transparency between booker and talent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MDL Token Now Trading on XBTS.io DEX</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2019-03-05-mdl-now-trading-on-xbts/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2019-03-05-mdl-now-trading-on-xbts/</guid>
      <description>It was never a secret that MDL Talent Hub prefers decentralized exchanges&amp;ndash;DEXs&amp;ndash;for listing, and as we were already trading on Waves DEX starting from the beginning of the project, we are now very happy to announce that MDL Token is also trading on yet another DEX: XBTS.io.
XBTS Decentralized Exchange is for everyone who wants to simply and securely buy and sell Bitcoins or Altcoins. Instant buy/sell of cryptocurrencies at fair price is blockchain-guaranteed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MDL Talent Hub - Development update 2019 (part I)</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2019-03-04-mdl-dev-update-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2019-03-04-mdl-dev-update-part-1/</guid>
      <description>We are happy to announce some important updates this week, including new versions of our desktop and mobile wallet and key improvements on the UX/UI front. This article though will only cover the first part. There&amp;rsquo;s more soon.
New features for the app are ready to go, from ways talents and bookers can post feedback on each other to payment management and messaging, as well as improved onboarding. Meanwhile, we’ve built full end-to-end scenarios for bookers, talents, agencies, and most importantly parents that will help us make the gig booking process better for everyone involved.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MDL New Year 2019 Chess opens today</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2019-01-19-mdl-new-year-2019-chess-tournament-opens-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2019-01-19-mdl-new-year-2019-chess-tournament-opens-today/</guid>
      <description>MDL New Year 2019 Chess opens today The MDL Global Chess Tournament officially starts now!
All the action and details on progress will be available in our telegram group.
Since the level of our participants varies quite a lot, we decided to divide the players into two groups &amp;ndash; pro and beginner. Basically, if you dare to say you&amp;rsquo;re a pro, you will need to be prepared to fight for the top 4 places in the group; the top 4 pros will face the top 4 beginners in the finals to fight for places 1-8.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MDL New Year 2019 Chess tournament starting soon</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2019-01-07-mdl-new-year-2019-chess-tournament-soon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2019-01-07-mdl-new-year-2019-chess-tournament-soon/</guid>
      <description>MDL New Year 2019 Chess tournament starting soon So the year has started, and any day now the MDL Global Chess Tournament will be starting too!
As soon as the last 10-15 people that we are aiming for join we will begin scheduling games on lichess, so be sure to sign up and compete for big MDL prizes if you haven’t already.
Here’s how it works:
 Join MDL Games and Tournaments Telegram Group</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MDL Android Wallet Beta Release</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2019-01-03-mdl-android-wallet-open-beta-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2019-01-03-mdl-android-wallet-open-beta-release/</guid>
      <description>MDL Android Wallet Beta Released and Localized! 10 years ago today the genesis block for the Bitcoin blockchain was generated.
That makes today a great day to announce the MDL Android wallet&amp;rsquo;s official release for open Beta testing on Google Play.
Just a month and a half ago we released our internal Android wallet in alpha channel, and where there were (minor) glitches before, now there are no more. Many thanks everybody who took part in internal testing to help fix hundreds of small bugs and make the many recommendations that were applied.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MDL Talent Hub Global New Year 2019 Chess Tournament</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-12-18-mdl-global-chess-tournament-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-12-18-mdl-global-chess-tournament-1/</guid>
      <description>MDL Talent Hub Global New Year 2019 Chess Tournament #1 Upset about crypto prices or global instabilities? MDL Talent Hub invites you to forget your worries by competing in our chess tournament next month!
This year the MDL Global Chess Tournament is celebrating all of the world’s New Year’s starting in early January and ending just after the lunar Year of the Pig arrives. We’ll be sending the official dates and instructions for setting up games as soon as enough players join, so sign up among the first 20 to make sure you get into the tournament.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MDL Talent Hub is Sustainable.</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-12-10-mdl-talent-hub-is-sustainable/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-12-10-mdl-talent-hub-is-sustainable/</guid>
      <description>MDL Talent Hub is Sustainable. This post is meant to address concerns about MDL Talent Hub Core Group’s viability these days, especially now that we are seeing such scary market prices. We have heard that many shitcoins and weak projects have terminated their businesses and many people associated with other cryptocurrencies are announcing major reductions in staff.
Throughout 2018, the crypto markets have experienced an unprecedented collapse and ALL altcoins have been particularly affected.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The MDL Talent Hub is releasing the Android Wallet on Google Play Store.</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-11-14-mdl-talent-hub-android-wallet-store/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-11-14-mdl-talent-hub-android-wallet-store/</guid>
      <description>MDL Talent Hub is releasing the Android Wallet on Google Play Store. Today marks a huge milestone on our path, the release of the Android Wallet on Google Play Store. We would like to invite you to join the testing program for an unreleased version of the MDL Wallet app.
Instalation steps:
 First allow to access your Camera so that the QR code reader can do its job of scanning QR codes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The MDL Talent Hub is Celebrating Golang 9 Years.</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-11-10-mdl-talent-hub-celebrating-golang-9years/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-11-10-mdl-talent-hub-celebrating-golang-9years/</guid>
      <description>MDL Talent Hub is Celebrating Golang 9 years old. Today marks the ninth anniversary of the day that Golang went open-sourced. We would like to take time to cheer and praise this amazing language that has provided so much to our community.
The past 12 months have been a breakout year for the MDL developers, our AMAZING community, and so for the Go language and community.
Why are we celebrating ?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MDL @Blockchance - Interviews.</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-09-06-mdl-talent-hub-at-blockchance-the-interviews/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-09-06-mdl-talent-hub-at-blockchance-the-interviews/</guid>
      <description> MDL Talent Hub at Blockchance - The interviews David Delgado - Android Developer Watch the interview: 
Roman - CTO  Thomas - CEO  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The MDL Talent Hub at Blockchance.</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-08-25-mdl-talent-hub-at-blockchance/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-08-25-mdl-talent-hub-at-blockchance/</guid>
      <description>MDL Talent Hub at Blockchance - By JoëL fiber-rider What motivated me? I attended a blockchain event for the first time and knew some projects from the internet. Full of anticipation, finally seeing some of the developers in real, I went to the event because of the new Blockchain Technology 3.0 from Skycoin. The ambitious goal to &amp;ldquo;combat&amp;rdquo; the usual Internet service providers aroused my interest to even think of Blockchain and the crypto currencies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TalkInAnElevatorDay</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-07-27-talkinanelevatorday/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-07-27-talkinanelevatorday/</guid>
      <description>#TalkInAnElevatorDay Did you know that today marks “National Talk in an Elevator Day”? Yes, you read it right. And we bet you had no idea that there is such day. It takes place on the last Friday of July every year, carrying the premise to encourage people to break the silence and make the conversation with a stranger while riding in an elevator.
We all know and experienced that awkward silence during a routinely quiet vertical commute.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About our YOYOW partnership</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-07-25-about-our-yoyow-partnership/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-07-25-about-our-yoyow-partnership/</guid>
      <description>About our YOYOW partnership In January 2018 MDL Talent Hub and YOYOW have concluded a strategic partnership agreement. The idea behind it is to integrate the MDL platform into YOYOWs ecosystem. What does this mean?
First of all, let’s quickly go over YOYOW’s mission. The guys at YOYOW are basically bringing instruments for fair distribution of value creation in social media networks. In traditional social media users never receive any material rewards for the content they create, which is absolutely unfair!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MDL Interview - Miss Yeah</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-07-19-mdl-interview-miss-yeah/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-07-19-mdl-interview-miss-yeah/</guid>
      <description>A fun and interesting interview with internet celebrity &amp;ldquo;Miss Yeah&amp;rdquo;!  What do you do if you have the opportunity to meet Miss Yeah? Interview her of course! On our second day at the RISE conference in Hong Kong, we had the opportunity to interview Miss Yeah, here is how that went:
  Thank you for taking some time off from your busy schedule to answer a few questions about your life &amp;amp; work</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ThisIsMe</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-07-18-thisisme/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-07-18-thisisme/</guid>
      <description>#ThisIsMe We all have a story to tell.  Being an artist, a model, or a dancer is getting more and more arduous nowadays. Talents are often misused, cheated, or simply treated poorly. Moreover, there is always a strict competition in the market. This, combined with the problems of business transparency and efficiency makes the talent and talent booking market more challenging than ever.
MDL Talent Hub was created to solve all these issues, connect talents, bookers, agencies, and brands and make a breakthrough in the talent sourcing industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MDL&#43;Sigma Partnership Announcement.</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-07-16-mdl-sigma-partnership-announcement/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-07-16-mdl-sigma-partnership-announcement/</guid>
      <description>MDL+Sigma Partnership Announcement.  MDL Talent Hub made another push forward with their goal of uniting talents, brands and agencies. And today we are happy to announce our new partnership and welcome Sigma onboard.
Founded in 2015, within only a few years, Sigma has become one of the most prominent model scouting agencies in Russia, having formed three basic directions such as photo shooting, modeling, and promo.
Now, Sigma can be called with no doubt as one of the leaders in the Russian model scouting market, already having more than 500 people in the team and over 50 offices across Russia and Belarus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summer is in full glory and so is bounty season!</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-07-10-bounty-announcement/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-07-10-bounty-announcement/</guid>
      <description>Summer is in full glory and so is bounty season! MDL Talent Hub is moving fast, and that means that we have a lot of materials that require some extra hands on deck. For this reason, we are announcing another bounty run!
We have all the rules and ways to participate explained HERE where you are also welcome to ask any additional questions!
We are looking for fresh articles, reviews, videos and other content that can help put MDL Talent Hub in the spotlight or provide useful information for people who don&amp;rsquo;t know about us yet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MDL Attending RISECONF 2018 HK</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-07-05-mdl-attending-riseconf-2018-hk/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-07-05-mdl-attending-riseconf-2018-hk/</guid>
      <description>It is that time of the year again, no it&amp;rsquo;s not in Silicon Valley, it is however, in China, Hong Kong! RISE Conference for those who don&amp;rsquo;t know, is on it&amp;rsquo;s 4th installment and is the biggest gathering of start-ups, entrepreneurs, investors, established tech brands, and tech thought-leaders in Asia.
It is for that exact reason, that we felt it extremely appropriate to showcase MDL Talent Hub and have a booth during the event.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MDL Token Distribution Announcement</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-06-28-mdl-token-distribution-announcement/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-06-28-mdl-token-distribution-announcement/</guid>
      <description>MDL Token Distribution Announcement MDL Bounty and token distribution is complete. This article will quickly recap what is going on and how you can check whether or not you received your tokens and what to do if you are still holding on to pre-MDL Tokens (Waves)!
In the past week
 We have been hard at work getting the tokens and bounty distributed to everyone who has supported us thus far and who has been waiting for their fair share of tokens.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The MDL Talent Hub at CIEF</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-06-27-mdl-talent-hub-at-cief/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-06-27-mdl-talent-hub-at-cief/</guid>
      <description>MDL Talent Hub at CIEF Our Team Attended The “China Innovation and Entrepreneur Fair” in Guangzhou last weekend. This is a short recap!
First of all, we have 2 event video recaps which you can watch here:
 MDL Talent Hub @CIEF Part 1
   MDL Talent Hub @CIEF Part 2
  Short Event Recap  MDL Talent Hub visited the China Innovation and Entrepreneurship Fair in Guangzhou last week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We Are MDL</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-06-20-we-are-mdl/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-06-20-we-are-mdl/</guid>
      <description>We Are MDL #1  The competition that keeps on giving.
 Ready your creative talents because here are some of the highlights of our first ever &amp;ldquo;We Are MDL&amp;rdquo; competition!
This is going to be a reocurring MDL Tradition to promote the talents of everyone in our great community! The rules are simple:
  Create a +/- 1 minute video Mention something you love about MDL Talent Hub Upload the video to social media with the hashtags #MDLTalentHub &amp;amp; #WeAreMDL Upload a screenshot of your post and the video HERE   And that&amp;rsquo;s all it takes to join our bi-weekly competition!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You should join the We Are MDL Competition!</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-06-26-you-should-join-the-we-are-mdl-competition/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-06-26-you-should-join-the-we-are-mdl-competition/</guid>
      <description>You should join the We Are MDL Competition! This is why.
First off is to show your talent to the world. Show something you love, what you have a flair for, what cheers you up and what you express your personality through.
Second off is to grab a chance to win MDL tokens. “What can I do with them?” — the common question that immediately pops up in the mind of most of the talents when they hear about MDL Talent Hub and our competition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MDL Talent Hub @ China Innovation and Entrepreneurship Fair!</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-06-19-china-innovation-and-entrepreneurship-fair/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-06-19-china-innovation-and-entrepreneurship-fair/</guid>
      <description>MDL Talent Hub @ China Innovation and Entrepreneurship Fair!  The 2018 China Innovation and Entrepreneurship Fair is finally here and MDL Talent Hub is joining!
 About The 2018 China Innovation and Entrepreneurship Fair (CIEF) will be held in Guangzhou from June 22 to June 24.
This year is going to focus on the infinite possibilities of today&amp;rsquo;s science and technological developments. MDL Talent Hub is a perfect example in how technology and offline activities can merge harmoniously to create a better future for todays talents!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to promote your brand in 2018</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-06-16-how-to-promote-your-brand-in-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-06-16-how-to-promote-your-brand-in-2018/</guid>
      <description>##[Event Recap] How to promote your brand in 2018
Another day, another successful MDL event!
This evening was all about how to promote your brand in 2018 and for the line up, we had some amazing speakers covering topics such as creative recycling, KOL management, working with talents and influencers and how to properly engage influencer audiences.
 A free flow of wine, appetizers and live music brought a great networking atmosphere between presentations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Promote Your Fashion Brand In 2018</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-06-15-how-to-promote-your-fashion-brand-in-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-06-15-how-to-promote-your-fashion-brand-in-2018/</guid>
      <description>How To Promote Your Fashion Brand In 2018 We are mid-2018 and it is time to catch you up on the type of developments that are up-and-coming and already here to change the way brands promote fashion in 2018 and the future.
MDL Talent Hub is bringing together influential speakers from the fashion industry during a lovely evening with a wine tasting and live band to inform you more about upcoming trends, innovations and ways of promoting your brand in 2018.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beware of scammers. MDL is not an ERC20.</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-05-25-beware-of-scammers-mdl-is-not-an-erc20/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-05-25-beware-of-scammers-mdl-is-not-an-erc20/</guid>
      <description>Beware of scammers. MDL is not an ERC20 MDL is not an ERC20, that’s not a token on Ethereum blockchain. MDL is powered by skycoin fiber tech: MDL has its own blockchain and explorer.
 Be aware of scams!
 We recently found out that scammers are using our webpage, and are writing people in person to buy tokens from them. They try to trick you with a smart-contract trading on Ethereum blockchain that claims they are from the MDL.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The MDL Talent Hub at TNW conference</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-05-24-the-next-web-tnw-mdl-talent-hub/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-05-24-the-next-web-tnw-mdl-talent-hub/</guid>
      <description>The MDL Talent Hub is staying on top of the latest tech trends at TNW conference. MDL Talent Hub is at The Next Web.
MDL team understands that world is changing and the technology is no longer an industry, its a underlying driver that changes and lead innovation on every single business around the globe.
The TNW Conference was a must have, and our Team was present, in Amsterdam 2018.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thriving in an internationally based company</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-05-17-thriving-in-an-internationally-based-company/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-05-17-thriving-in-an-internationally-based-company/</guid>
      <description>Thriving in an internationally based company — MDL Talent Hub leads the way MDL Talent Hub is working cross-borders and for many teams that can be challenging, tiresome and sometimes destructive for the company culture.
Not for MDL Talent Hub. When Dimitri Doronin, CEO at MDL Talent Hub put together the MDL team, he did so with the right knowledge in mind.
Well-managed teams Nowadays, team structures are already considered as an indispensable tool for achieving a companies&amp;rsquo; strategic goals and keeping them alive by creating an influx of new ideas, approaches, know-how and products or services that tend to be born in well-managed teams.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 4 P&#39;s MDL Talent Hub is solving.</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-05-09-the-4-pps-mdl-talent-hub-is-solving/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-05-09-the-4-pps-mdl-talent-hub-is-solving/</guid>
      <description>The 4 P&amp;rsquo;s MDL Talent Hub is solving. MDL Talent Hub is creating 3 ecosystems in 1 platform that will solve the problems of talent-bookers &amp;amp; agents, talents and brands.
The 4 main Problems MDL Talent Hub will address:
 Talents all over the world are experiencing problems in the talent-booking industry. On the other hand, companies, especially small-mid-size companies, are experiencing lower ROI&amp;rsquo;s than they should have when working with influencers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MDL was invited to speak at the 2018 Global Graphene Developer Conference!</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-05-08-mdl-was-invited-to-speak-at-the-2018-global-graphene/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-05-08-mdl-was-invited-to-speak-at-the-2018-global-graphene/</guid>
      <description>MDL was invited to speak at the 2018 Global Graphene Developer Conference!  5 MAY 2018 YOYOW, partners of MDL Talent Hub, invited us to speak at the GGDC in Shanghai. YOYOW was announcing their product launch at this event and invited MDL Talent Hub as guest speakers to explain the practical implications of their technology in a use case with the MDL Talent Hub ecosystem.
 Dimitri Doronin; CEO of MDL Talent Hub gave a presentation about MDL Talent Hub and how it can benefit the growth of the entertainment industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is the MDL Token Hour Economy?</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-05-06-what-is-the-mdl-token-hour-economy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-05-06-what-is-the-mdl-token-hour-economy/</guid>
      <description>Sky Fiber blockchain technology allows the accumulation of token hours for holders of MDL tokens. The mechanism is simple — if one has 1 MDL token, after 1 hour he or she gets 1 MDL token hour, if one has 10 MDL tokens, after 1 hour he or she gets 10 MDL token hours. The more MDL tokens you have and the longer you keep them, the more MDL tokens hours can be accumulated.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MDL Talent Hub influencers &amp; performers</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-05-05-mdl-talent-hub-influencers-performers-take-note/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-05-05-mdl-talent-hub-influencers-performers-take-note/</guid>
      <description>Why you should join MDL Talent Hub  MDL Talent Hub is platform that allows influencers and performers (Talents) from all ranges, beginners to professionals, to find gigs and connect with brands and agencies.
 What makes MDL Talent Hub unique is its collaboration with brands and agencies and the fact that it allocates a reputation to everyone using the platform (talents, brands &amp;amp; agencies). This is to fight issues in the performers-booking industry such as sexual harassment, overdue payments, harming of brand-image, …</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MDL &#43; DXD Partnership Confirmed!</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-05-03-mdl-dxd-partnership-confirmed/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-05-03-mdl-dxd-partnership-confirmed/</guid>
      <description>MDL + DXD Partnership Confirmed! Watch out entertainment industry! MDL Talent Hub is moving, and it&amp;rsquo;s moving fast!
Today we are happy to announce our partnership with DXD Entertainment.
DXD Entertainment  is a leading talent/model agency based in Seoul, Korea. Their main activities exist out of contacting celebrities, top talents, fashion models, actors, narrators, dancers, singers, musicians and performers from all over the world.
Their talents and models are in demand for editorials, advertisings, fashion runway, magazines, catalogues, movies, dramas, tv and radio commercials, corporate videos, music videos, educational materials, animation voiceovers, documentaries, commercial song recordings, games, apps, product launches, parties and exhibitions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MDL Development Strategy</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-05-04-mdl-development-strategy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-05-04-mdl-development-strategy/</guid>
      <description>MDL Development Strategy Development team at MDL have been working really hard to deliver the MVP, and the Architecture team has delivered UML diagrams that offers a number of benefits for our internal organization.
The Unified Modeling Language (UML) will help us to model MDL systems and help us to build software that is designed to be simple and easy to use.
At MDL, we are using UML diagrams because:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What are those wallets you keep hearing about?</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-04-25-what-are-those-wallets-you-keep-hearing-about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-04-25-what-are-those-wallets-you-keep-hearing-about/</guid>
      <description>What are those wallets you keep hearing about? It&amp;rsquo;s quite simple really.
 A blockchain wallet is a digital wallet that allows users to manage digital currencies. A blockchain Wallet is provided by a blockchain company
 [SHORT VERSION]
 A wallet is similar to the one in your pocket, but it&amp;rsquo;s located on your computer. It stores digital currencies or tokens. Each company can have its own wallet. MDL Talent Hub has its own wallet which you need to receive MDL Tokens.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 1st stage of MDL ITO nearly reached hardcap!</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-04-24-stage_1_ito_is_over/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-04-24-stage_1_ito_is_over/</guid>
      <description>MDL Has Nearly Reached Its Hardcap! It was tough, but we did it.
It was a critical decision to split the ITO into three stages and hopefully our community understood and welcomed the approach. We did this to better align our goals and increase our transparency. Showing our intentions and being clear about our long-term strategy is an important part in maintaining our relations with every MDL stakeholder.
The funds we were able to collect during the first stage will be enough to enhance our development activities as well as continuing marketing our platform to be even more presentable for our supporters and potential investors during the 2nd and the 3rd stages of the ITO.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>And on the 239th day MDL created the DEMO!</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-04-17-and-on-the-239-th-day-mdl-created-the-demo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-04-17-and-on-the-239-th-day-mdl-created-the-demo/</guid>
      <description>Yes, it is finally here! It has been 239 days since we started MDL Talent Hub and The MDL Talent Hub Platform demo has finally arrived in all its glory! Check out the video down below and we&amp;rsquo;ve also included an .apk file for you to try it out!
 If you want to try it out yourself, find the link to the application HERE
Enjoy and stay excited as MDL Talent Hub is moving forward day by day to bring you the best experience ever!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Early MDL investors can now swap their waves tokens!</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-04-16-investors-can-now-swap-their-waves-tokens/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-04-16-investors-can-now-swap-their-waves-tokens/</guid>
      <description>Good news everyone! Investors who bought Waves pre-MDL Tokens can now swap them in for Mainnet MDL!
Our developers have been hard at work to make this possible and they have delivered!
Swapping is made really easy, all you need to do is download the MDL wallet HERE (Press &amp;ldquo;Get MDL&amp;rdquo;) and you will be asked to download the MDL wallet.
Once there, you need to create a new wallet (Choose a name and save the seed somewhere safe) and when you select the type of currency you want to invest in exchange for MDL Tokens, you should choose &amp;ldquo;MDL.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Tech Is Taking Over The Fashion Industry</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-04-12-how-tech-is-taking-over-the-fashion-industry/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-04-12-how-tech-is-taking-over-the-fashion-industry/</guid>
      <description>How Tech Is Taking Over The Fashion Industry If you joined our rooftop event in Shanghai, you had the privilege of learning from 5 amazing speakers from the fashion industry that talked about how technology is changing their business landscape.
The speakers  Mr. Wang — chairman of Shanghai Garnment Group. Welcome speech with general introduction of the company + introduction of Hongqiao innovation centre with focus on blockchain</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Event Recap How Technology Is Changing The Fashion Industry</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-04-11-event-recap-how-technology-is-changing-the-fashion-industry/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-04-11-event-recap-how-technology-is-changing-the-fashion-industry/</guid>
      <description>[Event Recap] How Technology Is Changing The Fashion Industry Technology is everywhere, innovating fast and changing all aspects of our daily life. This is how technology is changing the fashion industry.
APRIL 09 2018: International Cultural Exchange and Innovation Center (ICECI), Shanghai Garment Group and MDL Talent Hub co-hosted an event about how blockchain technology is taking over global fashion industry. Each day technology is increasingly influencing our daily life and it is now also showing up more and more forever changing the trends in the fashion industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Micro-Influencers &gt; Macro-Influencers</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-04-10-micro-influencers-macro-influencers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-04-10-micro-influencers-macro-influencers/</guid>
      <description>Micro-Influencers &amp;gt; Macro-Influencers Today is about you, yes you! The rising stars, improvers, advisors, artists, visionaries, the ambitious women and men that are innovating the entertainment industry.
In this article we are taking a look at how micro-influencers are the rising stars of the entertainment industry and why more and more brands are reaching out to micro influencers rather than the big influencers.
Let start.
Micro-influencers, what are they? So what are micro-influencers?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10 ways to improve the talent-booking industry</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-04-03-10-ways-to-improve-the-talent-booking-industry/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-04-03-10-ways-to-improve-the-talent-booking-industry/</guid>
      <description>10 ways to improve the talent-booking industry If you have read our other articles, you will have seen that there are a lot of problems in this industry. We do mention how MDL Talent Hub is going to fix them, but here are 10 ways how, and why MDL Talent Hub is worth your time!
  MDL Talent Hub is for everyone.
By everyone we mean everyone! MDL Talent Hub aims to facilitate both the talents (Singers, Dancers, Actors, … ) and agents, but also the brands.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How is the platfrom protected from Token volatility</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-02-23-how-platform-is-protected-token-volatility/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-02-23-how-platform-is-protected-token-volatility/</guid>
      <description>Crypto currencies are known for their high fluctuating rates – daily trading range of 30% is not an unusual thing with these financial instruments, not to mention dumps and pumps that happen time to time. How can we deliver valuable tool to the talent sourcing market with MDL Token? The main contradiction lies in the conflict of actual platform users and crypto community – the first ones want to have stable economic ecosystem and the second ones want to speculate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Development Update</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-02-16-development-update-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-02-16-development-update-1/</guid>
      <description>Dear blockchain friends and MDL supporters.
The MDL Platform has been in the state of active development for quite some time now and the time has come to share some updates with the community.
We currently have around six ongoing dev projects within MDL. Some of them have been open source from day one (wallet, teller, the blockchain, blog, website), while others are being developed in-house and are tested internally (platform backend, android client, etc).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pre-ITO Hard Cap Is Reached!</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-01-31-pre-ito-hard-cap/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-01-31-pre-ito-hard-cap/</guid>
      <description>We believe MDL community is the most important stakeholder in the development of the platform - without you we are nothing! The presale hardcap is reached and that means we are doing the right things in the right time. MDL team is extremelly enthusiastic in bringing long-term value to the society and we are preparing more awesome stuff for the 2018. Stay tuned! Stay talented!
Truly yours, MDL.life</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why MDL Token Hours Are So Cool?</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-01-19-why-mdl-token-hours-are-so-cool/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-01-19-why-mdl-token-hours-are-so-cool/</guid>
      <description>MDL Talent Hub platform will be powered with MDL Token Hours (MDL TH). MDL TH will be used to support MDL Token value growth as well as to protect the platform from high MDL Token volatility. Below are 8 statements that describe MDL TH concept.
 The mechanism of MDL Token Hours has been adapted from Skycoin Coin Hours. The amount of MDL Tokens Hours received increases according to how many MDL Tokens are held.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why the value of MDL Token will increase over time</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-01-14-why-mdl-value-increase/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-01-14-why-mdl-value-increase/</guid>
      <description>For our early investors it is crucial to know why MDL tokens will increase in value over time. We have just realized that what was obvious to us is not that clear to the community. Here we briefly explain our plans about the usage of the Token and how we guarantee its growth for our crypto investors.
First of all, the value of the MDL token will increase from our expansion in the talent sourcing market, which is itself continually growing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anonymity and publicity in MDL Talent Hube</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-01-09-anonymity-publicity-in-mdl/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-01-09-anonymity-publicity-in-mdl/</guid>
      <description>One of our missions is to bring transparency to the talent sourcing market, however we also need to cope with the commonly accepted processes and settings in this area. Use of blockchain and Persistent Immutable Data Storage (PIDS) - IPFS, CXO - technologies that are known for their ability to make data open, traceable, and immutable raises a good question – what kind of information will be open to the public?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Approaches and Technical Decisions</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2017-12-31-approaches-technical-decisions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2017-12-31-approaches-technical-decisions/</guid>
      <description>Given the current state of global blockchain development, it seems that most people have totally forgotten that behind every project there are actual people working [or not]. So a stylish website with a promising, geeky video, featuring Bitcoin or Ethereum addresses, gets people more attracted to invest than a hardworking community with respect-worthy leaders. People just send money blindly to a smart contract, without researching who&amp;rsquo;s working on the concept, code, marketing, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Do We Do and Why</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2017-12-23-what-do-we-do-and-why/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2017-12-23-what-do-we-do-and-why/</guid>
      <description>What we are doing and why?
In the ongoing blockchain mania there are so many projects that seem to be less than genuine or even fake. ICOs have become not only a tool for startups to raise funds, but also for scammers looking to make a quick buck. Is MDL Talent Hub a real project with a well thought out vision and development plan, or it is just riding the wave of cryptohype?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MDL - Mine Distributed Ledger</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2017-12-21-mdl-mine-distributed-ledger/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2017-12-21-mdl-mine-distributed-ledger/</guid>
      <description>MDL Talent Hub will utilize PIDS technologies (IPFS, CXO, etc), which will allow information to be stored in a distributed manner on users’ devices and miners, improving access, speed, and security of information.
In order to compensate our users and miners we will establish a bounty program by which anyone can get a certain number of MDL Tokens for storing info about talents, events, and so forth. MDL Tokens can then be spent on MDL Talent Hub for other valuables or exchanged to other crypto or fiat currency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MDL at Skyledger Conference</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2017-12-14-mdl-at-skyledger-conference/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2017-12-14-mdl-at-skyledger-conference/</guid>
      <description>Since MDL Talent Hub is closely considering employing CXO technology and becoming a part of the Skyledger ecosystem, we were kindly invited to present our project to Shanghai blockchain enthusiasts and investors.
Skyledger is positioning itself as blockchain 3.0 and is strongly supported by business and IT communities. The technology is developed here in Shanghai by an international team and is aiming to overcome other DAO protocols.
MDL happy to be so close to one of the most advanced tech movements in China and the World.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pre-ITO Is Ongoing</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2017-12-13-pre-ito-is-ongoing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2017-12-13-pre-ito-is-ongoing/</guid>
      <description>In order to prepare for ITO, we require capital in the amount of $500.000. This amount will allow us to launch our ITO campaign in March, 2018, where we are expecting to rais $20m for the development of the platform, cross-border scaling and business development, as well as for R&amp;amp;D and further implementation of blockchain &amp;amp; PIDS technologies.
In January 2018 we are planning to conclude the Pre-ITO for the MDL Token.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>User Instruments - Part 1</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2017-12-08-user-instruments-part1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2017-12-08-user-instruments-part1/</guid>
      <description>Profile We believe that a talented person can be talented in many ways, so each profile will have several portfolios – actor, dancer, origami master, or whatever. Each of the portfolios will have sufficient presentation materials like compcard, intro videos, etc. Thus a booker can easily choose as specific portfolio from a talent as required for the certain event.
Search Search will be available both for bookers and talents so that it will possible for freelancers to look for jobs, and for bookers to find freelancers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MDL - My Daily Life</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2017-12-06-mdl-my-daily-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2017-12-06-mdl-my-daily-life/</guid>
      <description>For the last several decades the world&amp;rsquo;s economy has been experiencing a massive shift from agriculture and production based to services and creative based, as noted by Richard Florida, the head of the Martin Prosperity Institute, Canada. Modern technologies disrupt the economy in such a way that more and more people will be left unemployed. The change is so momentous that ideas which were previously considered insane such as that of unconditional basic income are already being implemented in advanced countries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How MDL secures reputation</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2017-12-05-how-mdl-secures-reputation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2017-12-05-how-mdl-secures-reputation/</guid>
      <description>In order to facilitate the credibility of reputation MDL Talent Hub will employ two modern technologies – blockchain and PIDS. Let us explain in a simple manner how it will work.
Persistent Immutable Data Storage (PIDS) is a new way to keep information. The technology allows storage of data on devices of users instead of using centralized servers which are vulnerable to attack. Nowadays there are two promising protocols being developed and already available for usage – IPFS and CXO; both promise to substantially reduce costs and increase the speed of transmission.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MDL Talent Hub at SF2017 Seoul</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2017-12-03-mdl-at-sf2017-seoul/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2017-12-03-mdl-at-sf2017-seoul/</guid>
      <description>Since South Korea is actively promoting the startup ecosystem and innovations to survive the fierce technological competition in Asia, the Korean government has initiated a program of annual startup festivals, and last week was the first successful trial. It was a gathering of entrepreneurs, tech media, and VCs all under one roof of the COEX complex in Seoul.
MDL Talent Hub was kindly invited to participate in the event and was lucky enough to gain some excellent exposure since the problems the project is aiming to solve exist in Korea as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Webpage is launched and MDL goes to Korea for SF2017.</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2017-11-25-webpage-is-launched-korea/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2017-11-25-webpage-is-launched-korea/</guid>
      <description>In the very beginning of December, the MDL Team will join Startup Festival 2017 in Seoul, South Korea. SF2017 is organized for the first time by the Korean government in order to facilitate an innovative ecosystem in the country. There will be around 60 chosen startups from Asia who have been personally invited to meet VCs and media from all around the world. MDL is on the list!
It will be the first big event for us as a team and we are looking forward to giving a nice impression to our potential partners as well as old friends that we will meet there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where will the money come from?</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2017-11-14-where-do-the-money-come-from/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2017-11-14-where-do-the-money-come-from/</guid>
      <description>In order to keep our financial flows positive we are considering the following methods of revenue creation. Innovative streams are enabled by the use of blockchain technology.
Traditional Streams
1.Extended functionality
Paid features will provide extended functionality for users of our platform. Extended functionality will allow bookers to be more knowledgeable and talents to be more presentable and thus it will give them both advantages on the market.
2.Commission from transactions</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What are we gonna do?</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2017-10-30-what-we-gonna-do/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2017-10-30-what-we-gonna-do/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lsquo;If I had an hour to solve a problem I&amp;rsquo;d spend 55 minutes thinking about the problem and 5 minutes thinking about solutions.&amp;rsquo; - Albert Einstein
 That especially applies to constantly evolving talent market that requires nonstop monitoring and analysis in order to be aware of constantly evolving issues. In addition, because solutions are not easy to develop, certain complications simply remain ignored. Thus not only identifying existing issues, but also foreseeing upcoming ones and taking preventive measures is necessary to allow one to be on the top of things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MDL team at Slush</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2017-10-13-mdl-team-slush-shanghai/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2017-10-13-mdl-team-slush-shanghai/</guid>
      <description>The first public appearance of MDL was on the 12th of October 2017 at Slush Conference. We presented our vision and ideas to several experienced VC investors and high-tech businessmen and not only got positive feedback and encouragement, but also received some valuable advice.
Excellent ideas cannot flourish in a closed off ecosystem, so sharing thinking and knowledge is absolutely important for survival and development in the modern world. It is said that social capital is much more important than any physical asset, so we were very happy to grow up our network by acquiring new valuable connections as well as strengthen our ties with old friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MDL inception (video)</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2017-10-10-mdl-inception/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2017-10-10-mdl-inception/</guid>
      <description>Your browser does not support the video tag.  It is said that some events have less probability to happen and some more. It looks like the event that took place on the 8th of October had pretty good chances to occur. All the puzzle pieces were collected in one place. It was a tiny step forward towards a great venture that is going to affect our society, and even more, the lives of its direct stakeholders.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The thing is</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2017-10-08-the-thing-is/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2017-10-08-the-thing-is/</guid>
      <description>The majority of Asian countries, including China and Indonesia, have already for the past several years been enthusiastically transforming their economies from export-driven to consumption-driven. Accordingly, the advertisement industry is expected to continue to show double digit growth. Taking into consideration collectivistic patterns of Asian cultures we can observe overwhelming involvement of talents in all marketing activities. No matter whether it is online, onscreen, or onsite promotion, talents are always a key element of advertising and promotional activities.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>