<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Development on MDL - Talent Hub Blog</title>
    <link>https://mdl.wtf/categories/development/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Development on MDL - Talent Hub Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://mdl.wtf/categories/development/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>MDL Desktop Wallet v0.27.1 Release</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2021-03-31-mdl-desktop-wallet-v0.27.1-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2021-03-31-mdl-desktop-wallet-v0.27.1-release/</guid>
      <description>We are happy to announce some important updates this week, including new versions of our desktop wallet and key improvements on the UX/UI front. This version of wallet supports Skycoin&amp;rsquo;s hardware wallet. Also includes all the features of Skycoin&amp;rsquo;s version 0.27.
The wallet has been updated from 0.26.1 -&amp;gt; 0.27.1, including changes and improvements in step with Skycoin wallet developments. Among the multiple updates are:
Added  Updated electron from version 2 to version 10, with many security fixes Add createRawTransactionV2 CLI command, which calls the API of /wallet/transaction to create the transaction and can create then unsigned transaction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MDL Development update - August</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2019-08-22-mdl-development-update-aug/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2019-08-22-mdl-development-update-aug/</guid>
      <description>MDL IOs Wallet is being developed We are super proud to announce that the new MDL IOs Wallet is being developed and its already functional. We are now in process of opening a new developer account on Apple store and getting all the approvals, so hang in there, this may take a little while! :)
We are going to walk you around, please feel free to grab a seat and enjoy the show!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MDL Development update - July</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2019-07-24-mdl-development-update-july/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2019-07-24-mdl-development-update-july/</guid>
      <description>MDL Android Wallet version 0.3.5 Released New version (0.3.5) of MDL Android Wallet just hit Google Play and available for everybody.
Several security improvements and bug fixes incorporated.
&amp;ndash;
Download MDL now and be part of our growing community, HERE IS HOW:
&amp;ndash;
1) Install the wallet from Google Play:
https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=live.mdl.wallet
 2) Send tokens:
 On this new release, the sending view shows USD price in Send screen as well as in each wallet details page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MDL Talent Hub - Development update 2019 (part III)</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2019-05-03-mdl-dev-update-part-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2019-05-03-mdl-dev-update-part-3/</guid>
      <description>This month we are happy to announce progress on UX design and business analysis and the completion of end-to-end flows for bookers, parents, agencies and talents.
While digital is changing the world of work, how you successfully grow your career in the digital age has become the hottest topic in international business. Our online business will help, further your career with communication and networking. Whether you’re a talent preparing to expand your network, or you’re looking for talents for supporting your projects, in this article, we will guide your way to achieve the goals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MDL Talent Hub - Development update 2019 (part II)</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2019-04-02-mdl-dev-update-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2019-04-02-mdl-dev-update-part-2/</guid>
      <description>In part one of our extended update for 2019 a few weeks ago we announced that we were starting migration to Desktop Wallet v0.25, along with other developments for the first part of the year. This time we are happy to bring news that migration is complete and v0.25 has launched, with new fixes and features that make trading MDL a better way to pay and be paid for any talent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MDL Talent Hub - Development update 2019 (part I)</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2019-03-04-mdl-dev-update-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2019-03-04-mdl-dev-update-part-1/</guid>
      <description>We are happy to announce some important updates this week, including new versions of our desktop and mobile wallet and key improvements on the UX/UI front. This article though will only cover the first part. There&amp;rsquo;s more soon.
New features for the app are ready to go, from ways talents and bookers can post feedback on each other to payment management and messaging, as well as improved onboarding. Meanwhile, we’ve built full end-to-end scenarios for bookers, talents, agencies, and most importantly parents that will help us make the gig booking process better for everyone involved.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MDL Talent Hub is Sustainable.</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-12-10-mdl-talent-hub-is-sustainable/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-12-10-mdl-talent-hub-is-sustainable/</guid>
      <description>MDL Talent Hub is Sustainable. This post is meant to address concerns about MDL Talent Hub Core Group’s viability these days, especially now that we are seeing such scary market prices. We have heard that many shitcoins and weak projects have terminated their businesses and many people associated with other cryptocurrencies are announcing major reductions in staff.
Throughout 2018, the crypto markets have experienced an unprecedented collapse and ALL altcoins have been particularly affected.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The MDL Talent Hub is releasing the Android Wallet on Google Play Store.</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-11-14-mdl-talent-hub-android-wallet-store/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-11-14-mdl-talent-hub-android-wallet-store/</guid>
      <description>MDL Talent Hub is releasing the Android Wallet on Google Play Store. Today marks a huge milestone on our path, the release of the Android Wallet on Google Play Store. We would like to invite you to join the testing program for an unreleased version of the MDL Wallet app.
Instalation steps:
 First allow to access your Camera so that the QR code reader can do its job of scanning QR codes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The MDL Talent Hub is Celebrating Golang 9 Years.</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-11-10-mdl-talent-hub-celebrating-golang-9years/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-11-10-mdl-talent-hub-celebrating-golang-9years/</guid>
      <description>MDL Talent Hub is Celebrating Golang 9 years old. Today marks the ninth anniversary of the day that Golang went open-sourced. We would like to take time to cheer and praise this amazing language that has provided so much to our community.
The past 12 months have been a breakout year for the MDL developers, our AMAZING community, and so for the Go language and community.
Why are we celebrating ?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MDL Development Strategy</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-05-04-mdl-development-strategy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-05-04-mdl-development-strategy/</guid>
      <description>MDL Development Strategy Development team at MDL have been working really hard to deliver the MVP, and the Architecture team has delivered UML diagrams that offers a number of benefits for our internal organization.
The Unified Modeling Language (UML) will help us to model MDL systems and help us to build software that is designed to be simple and easy to use.
At MDL, we are using UML diagrams because:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 1st stage of MDL ITO nearly reached hardcap!</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-04-24-stage_1_ito_is_over/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-04-24-stage_1_ito_is_over/</guid>
      <description>MDL Has Nearly Reached Its Hardcap! It was tough, but we did it.
It was a critical decision to split the ITO into three stages and hopefully our community understood and welcomed the approach. We did this to better align our goals and increase our transparency. Showing our intentions and being clear about our long-term strategy is an important part in maintaining our relations with every MDL stakeholder.
The funds we were able to collect during the first stage will be enough to enhance our development activities as well as continuing marketing our platform to be even more presentable for our supporters and potential investors during the 2nd and the 3rd stages of the ITO.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>And on the 239th day MDL created the DEMO!</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-04-17-and-on-the-239-th-day-mdl-created-the-demo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-04-17-and-on-the-239-th-day-mdl-created-the-demo/</guid>
      <description>Yes, it is finally here! It has been 239 days since we started MDL Talent Hub and The MDL Talent Hub Platform demo has finally arrived in all its glory! Check out the video down below and we&amp;rsquo;ve also included an .apk file for you to try it out!
 If you want to try it out yourself, find the link to the application HERE
Enjoy and stay excited as MDL Talent Hub is moving forward day by day to bring you the best experience ever!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Early MDL investors can now swap their waves tokens!</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-04-16-investors-can-now-swap-their-waves-tokens/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-04-16-investors-can-now-swap-their-waves-tokens/</guid>
      <description>Good news everyone! Investors who bought Waves pre-MDL Tokens can now swap them in for Mainnet MDL!
Our developers have been hard at work to make this possible and they have delivered!
Swapping is made really easy, all you need to do is download the MDL wallet HERE (Press &amp;ldquo;Get MDL&amp;rdquo;) and you will be asked to download the MDL wallet.
Once there, you need to create a new wallet (Choose a name and save the seed somewhere safe) and when you select the type of currency you want to invest in exchange for MDL Tokens, you should choose &amp;ldquo;MDL.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How is the platfrom protected from Token volatility</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-02-23-how-platform-is-protected-token-volatility/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-02-23-how-platform-is-protected-token-volatility/</guid>
      <description>Crypto currencies are known for their high fluctuating rates – daily trading range of 30% is not an unusual thing with these financial instruments, not to mention dumps and pumps that happen time to time. How can we deliver valuable tool to the talent sourcing market with MDL Token? The main contradiction lies in the conflict of actual platform users and crypto community – the first ones want to have stable economic ecosystem and the second ones want to speculate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Development Update</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-02-16-development-update-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2018-02-16-development-update-1/</guid>
      <description>Dear blockchain friends and MDL supporters.
The MDL Platform has been in the state of active development for quite some time now and the time has come to share some updates with the community.
We currently have around six ongoing dev projects within MDL. Some of them have been open source from day one (wallet, teller, the blockchain, blog, website), while others are being developed in-house and are tested internally (platform backend, android client, etc).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Approaches and Technical Decisions</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2017-12-31-approaches-technical-decisions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2017-12-31-approaches-technical-decisions/</guid>
      <description>Given the current state of global blockchain development, it seems that most people have totally forgotten that behind every project there are actual people working [or not]. So a stylish website with a promising, geeky video, featuring Bitcoin or Ethereum addresses, gets people more attracted to invest than a hardworking community with respect-worthy leaders. People just send money blindly to a smart contract, without researching who&amp;rsquo;s working on the concept, code, marketing, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MDL - Mine Distributed Ledger</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2017-12-21-mdl-mine-distributed-ledger/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2017-12-21-mdl-mine-distributed-ledger/</guid>
      <description>MDL Talent Hub will utilize PIDS technologies (IPFS, CXO, etc), which will allow information to be stored in a distributed manner on users’ devices and miners, improving access, speed, and security of information.
In order to compensate our users and miners we will establish a bounty program by which anyone can get a certain number of MDL Tokens for storing info about talents, events, and so forth. MDL Tokens can then be spent on MDL Talent Hub for other valuables or exchanged to other crypto or fiat currency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>User Instruments - Part 1</title>
      <link>https://mdl.wtf/en/2017-12-08-user-instruments-part1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mdl.wtf/en/2017-12-08-user-instruments-part1/</guid>
      <description>Profile We believe that a talented person can be talented in many ways, so each profile will have several portfolios – actor, dancer, origami master, or whatever. Each of the portfolios will have sufficient presentation materials like compcard, intro videos, etc. Thus a booker can easily choose as specific portfolio from a talent as required for the certain event.
Search Search will be available both for bookers and talents so that it will possible for freelancers to look for jobs, and for bookers to find freelancers.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>